gildshire.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy for Gildshire

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for Gildshire. The Gildshire Services may contain links to other websites for your convenience and information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites.

This Privacy Policy covers the following:

Information do we gather about you What we do with the information we gather about you Sharing of the information we gather Gildshire‘s email policy Changing or updating your personal information Email opt-out policy Protection of your information Compliance with legal process Children‘s Guidelines Your California Privacy Rights

INFORMATION DO WE GATHER ABOUT YOU

The information Gildshire gathers falls into two categories: 1) personal information, which includes personal information you supply when you subscribe, order, complete a survey, register for any Services, enter a contest, or provide your e-mail address and 2) non-personal information collected through technology, including tracking information collected when you utilize the Services.

Registration Information. Registration for Gildshire Services may require that you supply certain personal information, including a unique e-mail address and demographic information (e.g., zip code, age, gender) to register.

Billing and Credit Card Information. To enable payment on the Gildshire services, we may collect and store name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information and other billing information. This information will only be shared with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase transaction, such as fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments.

User Generated Content. We offer you opportunities to post content and engage in public activities through the Services. “Public activities” are any actions you take through the Services that are designed to be visible to other users, including comments, recommendations, ratings or any other items that you submit. Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your screen name or ID, or any image or photo, becomes public and may be used by Gildshire for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all Media. If you choose to engage in public activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other Service users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums, and Gildshire has no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your public activities or any of your submissions that are a result of your public activities.

When you share or recommend any Gildshire Content to your Facebook profile or other social media profile, that action is governed by Facebook‘s privacy policy or the privacy policy of the applicable social media platform.

If you have registered for aGildshire Account, we may track and aggregate your public activities on the Services. By choosing to participate in public activities, you are electing to share and display such public activities via the Services. Also, public activities may be included in RSS feeds, APIs, and made available to other websites via other formats. As a result, your public activities may appear on other websites, blogs, or feeds. Keep in mind that we are not responsible for any personal information you choose to make public via your public activities, and you agree that such sharing will be deemed to have been done by you, not Gildshire.

Contests, Sweepstakes and Special Offers. Gildshire may collect personal information from you in connection with optional sweepstakes, contests or special offers. If this information is also being collected by a third party other than Gildshire, we may notify you at the same time. If you do not want any personal information shared, you may always decline to participate in the sweepstakes, contest or special offer.

Special Events and Promotions. We often receive information regarding readers who may attend Gildshire conferences, events and promotions from sign-in and registration lists. Unless we indicate otherwise at the time we collect the information, we may use such information in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

Information Collected by Us Using Technology. We use various Internet technologies to manage Gildshire Services and track use of the Services. Non-personal information that we collect using these technologies may be combined with other information about you.

Device Information. We may collect non-personal information about the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access Gildshire Services, such as IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language and other transactional information.

Cookies, Beacons, Local Storage and Other Similar Technologies. In providing the Gildshire Services, we may use “cookies,” Web beacons, HTML5 local storage and other similar technologies to manage access to and use of the Services, recognize you and provide personalization, as well as to help us understand where our visitors are going and how much time they spend there. You may not be able to access certain aspects of the Services, including portions of the Site, if your computer does not accept cookies from us.

Analytics Technologies. Gildshire may hire third parties to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage, browsing patterns of Gildshire users. Google Analytics tracks and analyzes non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers on Gildshire. All data collected by Google Analytics on our behalf is owned and used by us. For more information about how Google Analytics collects data, please read their privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

IP Addresses. Gildshire may log Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to our websites and mobile applications.

Log Files and Your Reading History. Gildshire may automatically log certain usage information about your use of the Services, including a reading history of the pages you view on the Site.

We may use this information in order to provide you with customized recommendations on the Site based on your viewing history. We also use log files in the aggregate to analyze usage of our websites and mobile applications.

We may use this information in order to provide you with customized recommendations on the Site based on your viewing history. We also use log files in the aggregate to analyze usage of our websites and mobile applications. We do not have access to, nor control over, advertisers‘ or service providers‘ use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used. Your access to our websites should not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.

WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER ABOUT YOU

Providing the Services You Request. We use the information we gather about you to enable your use of the Services, fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling you to participate in and renew paid services, polls, contests, and message boards.

Statistical Analysis. We perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of the Services, and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base. We use this information for analysis purposes, including analysis to improve customer relationships.

Customizing Your Experience. We may use the information that we collect to allow advertising to be targeted to the users for whom such advertising is most pertinent. We may also use this information to customize certain features of Gildshire to provide you with an enhanced experienced based on the type of device you are using to access Gildshire, and in certain cases, provide you with requested services.

Relevant Advertising. We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on Gildshire Services to be targeted to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer‘s experience and the effectiveness of the ads. We disclose information to third parties only in aggregate or de-identified form.

E-Mail Newsletters. Gildshire will periodically send you e-mail newsletters or promotional e-mail about services offered by Gildshire and its advertisers.

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION WE GATHER

Gildshire Media. If you have registered to use the Services, we will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your e-mail address or any information that personally identifies you without your permission, unless otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy.

We also share information about our audience in aggregate or de-identified form. Nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to restrict Gildshire‘s use of aggregated or de-identified information in any way.

In the future, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, we may include your information among the transferred assets.

We reserve the right to disclose your opt-out information to third parties so they can suppress your name from future solicitations, in accordance with applicable laws. We may occasionally release personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena. (For more information, see the “Compliance with legal process” section of this policy.)

E-MAIL POLICY

We reserve the right to disclose your opt-out information to third parties so they can suppress your name from future solicitations, in accordance with applicable laws. We may occasionally release personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena. (For more information, see the “Compliance with legal process” section of this policy.)

E-Mail Newsletters. Gildshire offers e-mail newsletters and may offer more in the future. If you no longer wish to receive a specific newsletter, follow the “unsubscribe” instructions located near the bottom of each newsletter.

Survey E-Mail. We may send you an e-mail inviting you to participate in user surveys, asking for feedback on Gildshire and existing or prospective products and services, as well as information to better understand our users. User surveys greatly help us to improve Gildshire Services, and any information we obtain in such surveys will not be shared with third parties, except in aggregate form.

HTML E-Mail. When you sign up to receive e-mail from us, you will receive an HTML (with images) format. As such, we may place a one-pixel gif to determine whether or not readers viewed the e-mail. This process does not leave any information on your computer, nor does it collect information from your computer. Gildshire may share this data with others in aggregate only.

E-Mails From You. If you send us e-mails, you should be aware that information disclosed in e-mails may not be secure or encrypted and thus may be available to others. We suggest that you exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal or confidential information in e-mails. We may use your e-mail address to respond directly to your questions or comments.

Content Sharing Features. Gildshire may provide features in the Services that allow you to e-mail links to articles (or other Content) or post Content to social media platforms, such as Facebook. The e-mail addresses or other information that you supply in connection with such features are saved for your convenience for future Content you may wish to share; these addresses are not used for any other purpose, and will not be shared with any third parties.

E-MAIL OPT-OUT POLICY

E-Mail Promotions. If, at any time, you prefer not to receive e-mail marketing information from us, simply follow the unsubscribe options at the bottom of each e-mail.

Protection of Your Information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, technical and administrative controls to protect the information. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

Other Information

Compliance With Legal Process. We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of Gildshire Services; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

Children‘s Guidelines and COPPA Compliance. Gildshire does not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are the parent of guardian of a child under the age of 13, and you believe that Gildshire may have inadvertently collected personal information about your child, please contact Gildshire immediately at [info@gildshire.com](mailto:info@gildshire.com).

Children‘s Guidelines and COPPA Compliance. Gildshire does not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are the parent of guardian of a child under the age of 13, and you believe that Gildshire may have inadvertently collected personal information about your child, please contact Gildshire immediately at [info@gildshire.com](mailto:info@gildshire.com).

Changes to This Policy. This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If we make a significant or material change in the way we use your personal information, the change will be posted on this page thirty (30) days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via the e-mail address associated with the user‘s Gildshire Account.
